

EDUCATION

SEP 2012 - JUL 2017

Master's of engineering

Vinnytsia National Technical University- UA Brief Description: Electrical engineering and electromechanics

SEP 2021 - JUL 2022

C# .NET developer

Main Academy - UA

Brief Description: I have obtained a completed professional training in C#/.NET development at Main Academy, My projects on GitHub also demonstrate my knowledge of basic data structures, OOP methodology, and design patterns, working with interfaces and access modifiers, multithreaded applications, structures, typed dictionaries and lists, delegates and events, working with I/O and LINQ, handling exceptions, asynchronous code, and more.

CONTACTS

Phone: +380 63 1923793

Email: oleg.polinovskyi@gmail.com

Web:

linkedin.com/in/oleg-polinovskyi-59622918a

github.com/Linovskyi

Oleh Polinovskyi

Software developer engineer C#/.NET

ABOUT ME

I'm a 28 years old I have obtained a master's degree in Vinnytsia National Technical University and completed professional training in C#/.NET development at Main Academy. I believe that my knowledge and experience in this field, together with my willingness to learn and work in a team, will make me a valuable asset. I see my future in software development, and I am very eager to learn more about these technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IAN 2023

Junior C#/.NET Developer | Denmark

Softlocus, Kopenhagen

Brief Description: Fintech backend Development of accounting software using Scrum methodology

JAN 2022 - DEC 2022

Software developer Engineer C# .NET

Upwork, Kyiv

Brief Description: Software Development for the Internet of Things Worked with technologies such as AWS lot Core, Lambda, DynamoDB, EC2, RabbitMQ, C#/.Net 6, MS SQL, Web API, EF Core, Blazor, MAUI, Git, Postman This project is an internet platform for monitoring and managing the interaction between IoT devices. AWS IoT Core is used for collecting data from IoT devices and processing it. AWS Lambda stored in DynamoDB. RabbitMQ is used to facilitate communication between all the components of the system. The application is developed using C#/.Net 6 and uses MS SQL for data storage. Client side: Blazor, MAUI.

SEP 2017 - DEC 2021

Software developer Engineer

CSC-Automation LLC, Kyiv - UA

Brief Description: Development of automated control systems for technological processes

Professional Skills: .NET Framework/Core, CLR, C#, ORM Entity Framework, Dapper, MS SQL(T-SQL), DynamoDB, WPF, MAUI, Blazor, ASP.NET, MVC,API(CQRS+MediatR), SignalR, RabbitMQ, JS, Git, OOP, Docker, AWS EC2, AWS lot Core, Lambda, MQTT, JavaScript, OOP, SOLID, Clean Architecture, CSS, HTML, REST API and many other. Visual Studio, VS Code, SQL Server Management Studio, JetBrains Rider, ReSharper, dotPeek, dotMemory, Postman, Swagger, Hyper-V, TIA Portal, Step7, WinCC, TwinCat, Codesys, Genesis64, Movicon.